{
    "subject": "resource/BleachBit",
    "predicate": "ontology/programmingLanguage",
    "object": "resource/Python_(programming_language)",
    "human_readable": "BleachBit is written in Python.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.5623125433921814,
            "question": "What programming language is BleachBit written in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.376298189163208,
            "question": "What are some other programs written in Python?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.17375195026397705,
            "question": "Are there any alternatives to BleachBit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1447666734457016,
            "question": "What types of files can BleachBit clean up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1060623824596405,
            "question": "How does BleachBit work to clean up a computer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.10462942719459534,
            "question": "Can BleachBit be used to clean up your computer?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08488216996192932,
            "question": "What are some of the benefits of using open-source software like BleachBit?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.05411124229431152,
            "question": "Is Python a popular programming language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.049609165638685226,
            "question": "Is Python a high-level or low-level programming language?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04022962972521782,
            "question": "Why might someone choose to use Python for software development?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=BleachBit is written in Python.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8303_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Python a high-level or low-level programming language?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8303_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Python a popular programming language?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8303_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some of the benefits of using open-source software like BleachBit?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8303_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_3.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8303_98.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports this triple. The context mentions that \"BleachBit is written in Python, which is an interpreted language\". This confirms that BleachBit is indeed written in Python."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that \"BleachBit is written in Python, which is an interpreted language,\" and \"BleachBit was originally designed for GNU/Linux to free cache, delete cookies, clear Internet history, shred temporary files, delete logs, and discard junk you didn\u2019t know was there. It\u2019s the best Linux alternative to Windows\u2019 CCleaner.\" This information supports that BleachBit is written in Python."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}